<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Religion on Favorite Quotes</title><link>/tags/religion/</link><description>Recent content in Religion on Favorite Quotes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/tags/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do The Very Best That My Judgment Will Teach Me</title><link>/posts/do-the-very-best-that-my-judgment-will-teach-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/do-the-very-best-that-my-judgment-will-teach-me/</guid><description>If I ask him to give me wisdom concerning any requirement in life, or in regard to my own course, or that of my friends, my family, my children, or those that I preside over, and get no answer from him, and then do the very best that my judgment will teach me, he is bound to own and honor that transaction, and he will do so to all intents and purposes.</description></item><item><title>Doubt And Faith</title><link>/posts/doubt-and-faith/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/doubt-and-faith/</guid><description>Doubt isn&amp;rsquo;t the opposite of faith; it is an element of faith.
&amp;ndash; Paul Tillich, German theologian and historian</description></item><item><title>Fathers</title><link>/posts/fathers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/fathers/</guid><description>First of all, fathers are giving a name and a heritage to their children — clean and honorable. Fathers are for long, hard work, mostly their own kind of work; … for trying to give their children things [their] fathers never had. Fathers are for talking with, for encouraging, for putting arms around; for understanding mistakes, but not condoning them; for disciplining when needed, then loving all the more; for being strong and forceful, and for being tender and gentle.</description></item><item><title>If The Devil Says You Cannot Pray</title><link>/posts/if-the-devil-says-you-cannot-pray/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/if-the-devil-says-you-cannot-pray/</guid><description>If the Devil says you cannot pray when you are angry, tell him it is none of his business, and pray until that species of insanity is dispelled and serenity is restored to the mind.
&amp;ndash; Brigham Young (&amp;ldquo;Teachings of Presidents of the Church: Brigham Young&amp;rdquo;, p.45)</description></item><item><title>Let Your Adversity Count</title><link>/posts/let-your-adversity-count/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/let-your-adversity-count/</guid><description>If your pain and anguish end up taking you out — then it was all wasted. Let your adversity count for more than a reason to explain your defeat.
&amp;ndash; James MacArthur, President, BYU 10th Stake</description></item><item><title>Missionary Work &amp; Home Teaching</title><link>/posts/missionary-work-and-home-teaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/missionary-work-and-home-teaching/</guid><description>Missionary work is but home teaching to those who are not now members of the Church, and home teaching is nothing more or less than missionary work to Church members.
&amp;ndash; Pres. Harold B. Lee (&amp;ldquo;Preach My Gospel&amp;rdquo;, p.13)</description></item><item><title>Preach the Truth</title><link>/posts/preach-the-truth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/preach-the-truth/</guid><description>Preach the truth as you understand it. Do not speculate on things you know nothing about, for it will benefit no one.
&amp;ndash; Wilford Woodruff (&amp;ldquo;Teachings of Presidents of the Church: Wilford Woodruff&amp;rdquo;, p.61)</description></item><item><title>Public Teaching</title><link>/posts/public-teaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/public-teaching/</guid><description>In my public teaching I never permit my mind to follow in any channel except that which the Spirit dictates to me….
&amp;ndash; Wilford Woodruff (&amp;ldquo;Teachings of Presidents of the Church: Wilford Woodruff&amp;rdquo;, p.59)</description></item><item><title>The Gospel</title><link>/posts/the-gospel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/the-gospel/</guid><description>[The Gospel] embraces all morality, all virtue, all light, all intelligence, all greatness, and all goodness. It introduces a system of laws and ordinances.
&amp;ndash; Brigham Young (&amp;ldquo;Discourses of Brigham Young&amp;rdquo;, 3)</description></item><item><title>This Is Our Day</title><link>/posts/this-is-our-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/this-is-our-day/</guid><description>I believe that God has opened up these treasures of intelligence [technology] to enhance his purposes on the earth.
&amp;ndash; James E. Faust (source)</description></item><item><title>We Have A Mission In The World</title><link>/posts/we-have-a-mission-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/we-have-a-mission-in-the-world/</guid><description>We have a mission in the world: each man, each woman, each child who has grown to understanding or to the years of accountability, ought… to be qualified to preach the truth, to bear testimony of the truth.
&amp;ndash; Pres. Joseph F. Smith (&amp;ldquo;Preach My Gospel&amp;rdquo;, p.12)</description></item><item><title>What Would Jesus Do?</title><link>/posts/what-would-jesus-do/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/what-would-jesus-do/</guid><description>There in the Gospel as recorded by St. John, I found the clear and certain answer: Jesus would always do the will of his Father…. &amp;ldquo;For I do always those things that please him&amp;rdquo; [John 8:29].
&amp;ndash; President Marion G. Romney</description></item></channel></rss>